Interfaith Worker Justice Records 6414
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Faith Politics, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 61)
- Young Christian Workers, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 62)
- Call to Action Detroit, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 63)
- File, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 64)
- Servants of Mary, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 65)
- Work Responsibility Act (Clinton), 1997 (Box 22, Folder 66)
- Lawsuit Press Conference, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 67)
- Holy Cross Worcester, MA, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 68)
- Townsend Poultry Laurel Maryland, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 69)
- SC Ministry Foundation Sisters of Charity, Cincinnati, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 70)
- Wichita, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 71)
- UFCW Adv. Mtg Naples, FL, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 72)
- Highlander-Mexico, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 73)
- Techuacan Fact Finding, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 74)
- AFL-CIO meeting, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 75)
- DOL meeting, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 76)
- Sarah's Circle, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 77)
- MT AFL-CIO, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 78)
- WI Community Service, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 79)
- IL Income Taxes, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 80)
- Immokalee, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 81)
- Nashville UFCW, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 82)
- UFW, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 83)
- Muste, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 84)
- Unitarian Universalist Funding, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 85)
- SEIU 1199 Cincy, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 86)
- CHA New Orleans, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 87)
- Meth Fed for Social Action, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 88)
- Portland/Eugene OR, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 89)
- Poultry Festival, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 90)
- AFL-CIO meeting, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 91)
- UFCW Conference, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Chicago Retreat Jul 31-Aug 2, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- LCWR, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 3)
- National Baptist Convention, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 4)
- AFL-CIO IL State Convention, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 5)
- MACD - (Slope), 1998 (Box 23, Folder 6)
- SEIU - Local 25, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- Welfare to Work Meeting, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- DC, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 9)
- MASW, Springfield MO, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 10)
- Twin Cities Rel Labor Network, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 11)
- Wheaton College, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 12)
- Chicago Priests, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 13)
- Tides Foundation Meeting, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 14)
- Yale, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 15)
- NCC - Stony Point, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 16)
- UMC Quoadrennium Meeting, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 17)
- Little Rock Ft. Smith, Arkansas, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 18)
- Milwaukee, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 19)
- Chicago IRRA, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 20)
- Madison, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 21)
- NYC Trip Jan 9-12, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 22)
- United Students Against Sweatshops, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 23)
- Wheaton, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 24)
- Kalamazoo, MI, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 25)
- New Orleans, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 26)
- Notre Dame, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 27)
- Immokalee, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 28)
- Advocacy Consultation Planning Team, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 29)
- Roundtable, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 30)
- Jobs wit Justice, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 31)
- DC Delmarva, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 32)
- Associated Colleges, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 33)
- LSA - Cleveland, OH, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 34)
- PIIR Chicago, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 35)
- Spirited Women in Action, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 36)
- Ethics of Wages, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 37)
- United for a Fair Economy, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 38)
- UCC Eco Justice Providence, RI, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 39)
- LSTC Workshop, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 40)
- Call to Action, 2001 (Box 23, Folder 41)
- ELCA, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 42)
- Jubilee Justice, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 43)
- Midwest School for Workers, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 44)
- AFL-CIO Conference Chicago, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 45)
- Miami, FL, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 46)
- Detroit - Labor Day, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 47)
- Wash Action, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 48)
- Nov 3, - St. Charles, MO, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 49)
- Greensboro Justice Fund, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 50)
- AFSCME 11/13 Springfield, IL, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 51)
- NY State Conference Albany, NY, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 52)
- Boston Service Learning, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 53)
- Youngstown 11/23, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 54)
- Chicago DOL, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 55)
- Discussion Group 12/5, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 56)
- Rockford 12/9, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 57)
- Farm Workers - Albany 12/14, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 58)
- DC Solidarity Meeting 12/15, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 59)
- Lincoln Racine, WI 12/17, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 60)
- Forging Partnerships for a new Millennium, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 61)
- National Interfaith Committee, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 62)
- "The Plan", 2000 (Box 23, Folder 63)
- Regal Baltimore, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 64)
- IRRA - Harvard 1/9, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 65)
- Right to Org. - Milwaukee, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 66)
- Mother Guerin High School 2/26, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 67)
- Cincinnati Interfaith 2/24, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 68)
- UUJEC Workshop 3/3, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 69)
- USCC, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 70)
- Working Women's Conference, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 71)
- Presbyterian Women Daytona Beach, FL, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 72)
- JCUA 3/22, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 73)
- Kitchen Cabinet 4/8, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Building Trades 4/5, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 2)
- DePaul talk 5/4, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 3)
- National Campaign for Jobs and Income Support, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Clinic 5/5, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- Working for America Institute NYC. 5/15, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 6)
- DePaul Class - Spring, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 7)
- Global Economics - UCC, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 8)
- SEIU 5/21-22, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 9)
- San Francisco/Las Vegas 5/24-26, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 10)
- Immigration Forum 6/3, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 11)
- Social Welfare Action Alliance 6/23, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 12)
- Charlotte 6/24-25, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 13)
- Rivier College New Hampshire, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 14)
- NAEIS - Seattle 7/11, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 15)
- United Way Award 7/12, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 16)
- DC Poultry Meeting 7/18, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 17)
- CLC Advisory Committee, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 18)
- JWJ 7/21-23, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 19)
- Carpenters Convention 8/23, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 20)
- Community Services - Chicago 9/16, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 21)
- Daily Point of Light 9/19, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 22)
- Clue - LA 9/25-26, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 23)
- San Diego, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 24)
- UAW - Black Lake 10/10, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 25)
- Minneapolis/St. Paul RC P+J 10/24, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 26)
- Notre Dame 11/12, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 27)
- Champaign - Urbana 11/16, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 28)
- FMCS meeting 12/13, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 29)
- CTU - 1/11, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 30)
- Duluth, MN 1/25, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 31)
- Tides Foundation 1/19, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 32)
- Columbus 1/29, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 33)
- Labor - Mgmt. 2/26, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 34)
- UUJEC, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 35)
- Sacramento 3/8, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 36)
- Faith Works, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 37)
- NYC 3/12-14, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 38)
- Pittsburgh 3/20, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 39)
- Kitchen Cabinet 3/24, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 40)
- Working Class Meeting 4/2, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 41)
- AFL-CIO 4/18, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 42)
- Minneapolis 5/1-2, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 43)
- DSA Dinner 5/4, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 44)
- Buffalo 5/12, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 45)
- Champaign - Urbana 5/17, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 46)
- Lefties Discussion 6/2, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 47)
- DC Min Wage Press Conference 6/13, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 48)
- Calemet 6/21, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 49)
- NAES meeting Quad Cities, IA 7/8-10, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 50)
- Sun Times Ed Bd meeting, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 51)
- St. Theresa - July 19, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 52)
- Ergo Rally 9/20, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 53)
- CWU - Milwaukee, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 54)
- Orange County 8/7, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 55)
- Rabbinic School Gathering 8/15, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 56)
- JwJ Cleveland, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 57)
- Labor Day, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 58)
- Islamic Conference 9/12, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 59)
- SEIU 10/9, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 60)
- NY Labor - Religion 10/14-15, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 61)
- Milwaukee 10/18, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 62)
- Minneapolis Cedar Rapids 10 - 25/26, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 63)
- Iowa City 10/26, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 64)
- Naperville 10/30, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 65)
- ILSA Conference 10/30, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 66)
- Call to Action 11/3, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 67)
- Islam Worker Justice 11-10, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 68)
- DC - Nov 9-11, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 69)
- Higgins Dinner, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 70)
- Nashville Poultry legal meeting 11/9, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 71)
- Catholic Charities 11/30, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 72)
- Scope 1/15, 2002 (Box 24, Folder 73)
- UCLA 1/17-19, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 74)
- Racism Training 2/20, 2002 (Box 24, Folder 75)
- Worker Center Meeting 3/18-19, 2002 (Box 24, Folder 76)
- Seminarians 3/2, 2002 (Box 24, Folder 77)
- Macalester College 3/7, 2002 (Box 24, Folder 78)
- Steelworker - Indy 3/15, 2002 (Box 24, Folder 79)
- Rochester, 2002 (Box 24, Folder 80)
- Caregivers Meeting DC 2/27, 2002 (Box 24, Folder 81)
- DC - 4/10-12, 2002 (Box 24, Folder 82)
- CWU 4/9, 2002 (Box 24, Folder 83)
- UFCW - Chicago 4/24, 2002 (Box 24, Folder 84)
- Council on Foundations Meetings 4/29-30, 2002 (Box 24, Folder 85)
- Lawyers Conference 4/30, 2002 (Box 24, Folder 86)
- Blue Mountain Retreat NY 5/30-6/2, 2002 (Box 24, Folder 87)
- Campaign for Better Health Care 12/8, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 88)
- Interfaith Groups 12/11-12, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 89)
- Glenn Communications, 2002 (Box 24, Folder 90)
- Shaws Arrest - Worcester MA 6/19, 2002 (Box 24, Folder 91)
- Syracuse 6/23, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- CA Retreat 6/26, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Scupe Campus Ministries, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 3)
- Pax Christi, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- AFSCME - Boston 7/29, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- LACLAA Return 8/2, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 6)
- Muslim Conference 8/15, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 7)
- Call to Action Consulting 8/29, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 8)
- St. Nicholas Evanston - 9/1, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 9)
- 10/10-11, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 10)
- Harvard Jim Wallis, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 11)
- Leadership Gathering Chicago 10/20-22, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 12)
- NC - 11/1, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 13)
- SLC Des Moines 11/15, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 14)
- UCLA 1/17-19, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 15)
- AAR-SBL 11/22, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 16)
- Toronto, Canada 11/23-26, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 17)
- DC Event Dec. 10, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 18)
- Islam Worker Justice 12/12, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 19)
- FR Dinner, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 20)
- Notre Dame 1/7, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 21)
- Scupe - 1/16, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 22)
- Madison 2/17, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 23)
- Epis Urban Caucus 2/26-31, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 24)
- Miami 3/8-10, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 25)
- Scupe Action 3/14, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 26)
- AFSCME 3/28, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 27)
- Community - Labor Alliances AFL-CIO 4/4 Chicago, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 28)
- Springfield, MA 4/25, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 29)
- ELCA 5/7, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 30)
- Ford Rel Waren 5/13-14, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 31)
- Building Bridges 5/15, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 32)
- National Conference May, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 33)
- CID Bd meeting MLA 7/10, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 34)
- NAEIS Dayton Beach 7/22, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 35)
- UFCW Convention 8/1, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 36)
- Ford Convening 8/4-5, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 37)
- Sheet metal Workers Union 8/8 Philadelphia, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 38)
- Seminary Summer Debrief, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 39)
- Roach/Flanagon Home Party 9/10, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 40)
- Marx Outing 9/19-20, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 41)
- Marilyn Clement Hire Party 9/23, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 42)
- DC - Imam Meeting 9/24, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 43)
- Employment Justice Center 9/25, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 44)
- Louisville - Oct 1-2, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 45)
- Cleveland Hire Party UCC Meetings, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 46)
- Ms. Foundation Austin 10/10-12, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 47)
- Las Vegas 10/13-14, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 48)
- St. Olaf's Faith Work 10/16, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 49)
- Los Angeles 10/27-28, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 50)
- Greensboro, NC 11/1-2, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 51)
- Boston 11/4, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 52)
- Temple Israel 11/14, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 53)
- UMC Quadrennial 11/20-23, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 54)
- Atlanta -Teamsters 12/12, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 55)
- MAS ICNA 12/27, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 56)
- Notre Dame students 11/7, 2004 (Box 25, Folder 57)
- Religious Perspectives on Work 1/8, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 58)
- LSTC 1/20, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 59)
- Religious Perspectives Connie Meeting 1/26, 2004 (Box 25, Folder 60)
- Institute for Women's Policy 1/28 DC Research, 2004 (Box 25, Folder 61)
- Dallas - 2/16, 2004 (Box 25, Folder 62)
- NYC Trip 2/19-20, 2004 (Box 25, Folder 63)
- Northwest Arkansas 2/27-29, 2004 (Box 25, Folder 64)
- Arkansas House Party, 2004 (Box 25, Folder 65)
- 2004 (Box 25, Folder 66)
- Gainesville, Orland FL 3/1-2, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- San Francisco 3/4-5, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 2)
- Chicago Bd meeting 3/11, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 3)
- Funding Meeting 3/15, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Chicago Cintas Delegation 3/16-17, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 5)
- J-term Planning 3/25, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 6)
- Parliament of World Religions 3//30, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 7)
- NY Trip 4/1-2, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 8)
- Media Ford Faith 4/2, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 9)
- DePaul Religions Studies 4/16, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 10)
- Spirit Solidarity Forum 4/17, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 11)
- UALE Conference - Clothes 4/17, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 12)
- Seafarers International 4/26, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 13)
- Debs Dinner 6/7, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 14)
- Friends of NICWJ 5/11, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 15)
- Kentucky Poultry Meeting 5/15, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 16)
- Worker Center Meeting - DC 5/20-21, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 17)
- Austin, TX 5/24-25, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 18)
- WILG Conference St. Louis 4/29-30, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 19)
- Take Back Your Time 6/12, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 20)
- Seminary Summer/CST 6/13-18, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 21)
- Institute for Labor Studies Providence 6/17, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 22)
- Press Conference Cintas 6/23, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 23)
- Cincinnati 6/22-27, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 24)
- CA Trip 7/4-8, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 25)
- CA Trip July, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 26)
- Staff Retreat 7/12-13, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 27)
- Roundtable 7/29, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 28)
- ILSA Meeting 8/22-27, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 29)
- ILSA Conference (Regina) 8/23, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 30)
- Labor Day - United Church of Rogers Park 9/5, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 31)
- Religion Politics DC 9/13, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 32)
- Larry Fox, SEIU 1/27, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 33)
- Casey Meeting in CA 9/23, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 34)
- Chicago Interfaith Board Meeting 10/8, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 35)
- Cincinnati Oct 4, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 36)
- Media Consortium 10/6, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 37)
- Loras College, Dubuque Iowa 10/12, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 38)
- The Economy Immigrants 10/18, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 39)
- Sara Hespenian 10/19, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 40)
- Reform Movement 10/24, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 41)
- Directors' Council Meeting 10/25-26, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 42)
- Casey reception11/7, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 43)
- Boston-Curriculum, Nov 10-12, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 44)
- WILG 11/13, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 45)
- Jane Ramsey Benefit 11/13, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 46)
- Radio Interview 12/1, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 47)
- State National Religious Leaders DC 12/2, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 48)
- David Rhoads 1/6, 2005 (Box 26, Folder 49)
- Society of Christian Ethics 1/7, 2005 (Box 26, Folder 50)
- Scupe Class 1/11, 2005 (Box 26, Folder 51)
- J-Term Chicago Jan, 2005 (Box 26, Folder 52)
- Denner, Jan 14-15, 2005 (Box 26, Folder 53)
- Poultry Press Conference 1/25, 2005 (Box 26, Folder 54)
- Replenishing Democracy New Orleans 1/28-30, 2005 (Box 26, Folder 55)
- Casey Foundation Feb 3-4, 2005 (Box 26, Folder 56)
- DC Trip 2/17-19, 2005 (Box 26, Folder 57)
- Meeting with Mr. Sweeney 2/18, 2005 (Box 26, Folder 58)
- DePaul Sweatshops 3/2, 2005 (Box 26, Folder 59)
- Louisville 3/11-12, 2005 (Box 26, Folder 60)
- WILG 3/4, 2005 (Box 26, Folder 61)
- WI Deacons Meeting 3/5, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 62)
- Low Wage Work NYC 3/18-19, 2005 (Box 26, Folder 63)
- Restricted meeting minutes: Closed until 01Jan17 (Box 27)
- Restricted meeting minutes: Closed until 01Jan18 (Box 28)
- Restricted meeting minutes: Closed until 01Jan19 (Box 29)
- Restricted meeting minutes: Closed until 01Jan21 (Box 30)
- Restricted meeting minutes: Closed until 01Jan22 (Box 31)
- Restricted meeting minutes: Closed until 01Jan23 (Box 32)
- Restricted meeting minutes: Closed until 01Jan24 (Box 33)